<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="DILCISVocabularies.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<Vocabularies xmlns="https://DILCIS.eu/XML/Vocabularies/IP">
    <Vocabulary Name="ContentInformationTypeSpecification">
        <Information>
            <p>Vocabulary derived from E-ARK</p>
        </Information>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">ERMS</Term>
            <Definition>A predecessor to the CITS specification for Electronic records management is used.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">SIARD1</Term>
            <Definition>The content is a relational database described with SIARD version 1.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">SIARD2</Term>
            <Definition>The content is a relational database described with SIARD version 2.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="eb">SIARDDK</Term>
            <Definition>The content is a relational database described with SIARD version DK.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">GeoData</Term>
            <Definition>A predecessor to the CITS specification for Geodata is used.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citscarchival_v1_0</Term>
            <Definition>Version 1.0 of the Specification for E-ARK Content Information Type Specification for Archival Information (CITS Archival Information) is used.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citserms_v2_1</Term>
            <Definition>Version 2.1 of the Specification for the E-ARK Content Information Type Specification for Electronic Records Management Systems (CITS ERMS) is used to describe the content.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citspremis_v1_0</Term>
            <Definition>Version 1.0 of the Specification for the E-ARK Content Information Type Specification for Preservation Metadata using PREMIS (CITS PREMIS) is used.</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citsehpj_v1_0</Term>
            <Definition>Version 1.0 of the Specification for the E-ARK Content Information Type Specification for Patient Journals (CITS eHealth1) is used</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citsehcr_v1_0</Term>
            <Definition>Version 1.0 of the Specification for the E-ARK Content Information Type Specification for Cancer Registry export (CITS eHealth2) is used</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citssiard_v1_0</Term>
            <Definition>Version 1.0 of the Specification for the E-ARK Content Information Type Specification for Relational Databases using SIARD (CITS SIARD) is used</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">citsgeospatial_v3_0</Term>
            <Definition>Version 3.0 of the </Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">MIXED</Term>
            <Definition>A mixed set is described</Definition>
        </Entry>
        <Entry>
            <Term lang="en">OTHER</Term>
            <Definition>A term other than present in the vocabulary is used</Definition>
        </Entry>
    </Vocabulary>
</Vocabularies>